{
    "subject": "resource/Dorothea_Baird",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Teddington",
    "human_readable": "Dorothea Baird was born in Teddington.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9163623452186584,
            "question": "Is Dorothea Baird still living in Teddington?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8783677816390991,
            "question": "Where was Dorothea Baird born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8754014372825623,
            "question": "What year did Dorothea Baird live in Teddington?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8664925694465637,
            "question": "When was Dorothea Baird born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6906556487083435,
            "question": "Where did Dorothea Baird grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6610816717147827,
            "question": "Is Dorothea Baird a famous person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6185165643692017,
            "question": "What is Dorothea Baird known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48858198523521423,
            "question": "What is Dorothea Baird's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43112632632255554,
            "question": "Does Dorothea Baird have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3764552175998688,
            "question": "Did Dorothea Baird travel to other countries?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dorothea Baird was born in Teddington.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8576_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Dorothea Baird have any siblings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8576_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Dorothea Baird's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8576_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Dorothea Baird known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8576_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8576_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8576_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8576_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8576_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8576_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8576_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8576_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8576_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8576_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8576_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n\"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports Dorothea Baird being born in Teddington, as mentioned in the file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8576/re-ranker-msmarco/13.txt and 20.txt."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}